Guide to the Tree Top, Inc. Records 1938-2009
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 4: History, 1938-2008
  - Subseries 4.2: Photographs
    - Advertising: Television and retail displays
      - Black and white photos of television personalities Bozo the Clown--Los Angeles and Colorado Springs, CO; Popeye--Los Angeles, Spokane, and San Francisco; Tom Hatto; Engineer Bill--Los Angeles; Sheriff John-- Los Angeles; Fireman Frank; Marion Rowe; Helen Wade--Sacramento, CA; Art Finley--Stockton, CA; Jerry the Giraffe--Denver; Fred and Fae--Colorado Springs, CO; Sheriff Scotty--Denver; Gold Dust Charlie--Denver; Buddy Johnson of the "Big Mac Show"--Pueblo, CO; Skipper Frank--Los Angeles; Pete Perlaine-Billings, MT; JP Patches-Seattle; Brakeman Bill; Johnny Downs--San Diego; Deputy Dave; Wallace Sneed-- Phoenix; Corris Guy; Harvest Display; Ed Riemers; Chuck Waggin--Tucson, AZ; Captain Fortune--San Francisco; Marshall K. Gunn--Tucson, AZ; Fireman Joe; Buckskin Bill; Uncle Henry Dupre; Walker Edminston of "Little Rascals"; Mayor Carl; Unnamed personality, 1956-1959 (Box 11, Folder 04.15.03-04.15.05)
      - Executives with boxes of Tree Top juice, Circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 04.15.06)
      - Executives in Denver, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 04.15.06)
      - Stills from animated Tree Top commercials (8 items), 1956-1960 (Box 11, Folder 04.15.06)
      - Girl drinking apple juice (composite of negative and color transparency) (Box 11, Folder 04.15.06)
    - Plant and Production Photos
      - Plant equipment (4 items), Undated (Box 11, Folder 04.16.01)
      - Two color photos of Selah plant equipment, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 04.16.01)
      - Four color photos of Charbonneau Tree Top trucks, Circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 04.16.01)
      - Photo of apples on conveyor (2 items), Circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 04.16.01)
      - Two color photos of Charbonneau Tree Top storage room, Circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 04.16.01)
      - Two color photos of workers stacking boxes on pallets, Circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 04.16.01)
      - Black and white aerial photo of Cashmere plant, Undated (Box 11, Folder 04.16.02)
      - Black and white aerial photos of Wenatchee plant, Undated (Box 11, Folder 04.16.03)
      - Black and white aerial photos of Selah plant, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 04.16.04)
      - Color aerial photos of Corporate Headquarters and Selah and Ross plants, Undated (Box 11, Folder 04.16.05)
      - Color aerial photos of unidentified plants, Circa 1970 (Box 11, Folder 04.16.05)
      - Color proof sheets for aerial photos, Circa 1970 (Box 11, Folder 04.16.06)
      - Color photos of Corporate Headquarters, Undated (Box 11, Folder 04.16.06)
      - Black and white photos of Selah plant. Al Silveria, photographer (11 photos with accompanying letter), 1972 April (Box 11, Folder 04.16.06)
      - Envelope addressed to Eston C. Crain with three black and white photos of plant equipment, Undated (Box 11, Folder 04.16.06)
      - Cathie Clagg holding dried apples, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 04.16.07)
      - Apple peeler at Prosser, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 04.16.07)
      - Linda Welch driving a forklift, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 04.16.07)
      - Rosemary Seahorn holding water hose, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 04.16.07)
      - Black and white photos of women working on the assembly line, Undated (Box 11, Folder 04.16.07)
      - 14 black and white photos by Harold Laney of equipment and processing from washing apples to boxing juice cans, Undated (Box 11, Folder 04.16.07)
      - Three black and white photos of artists' rendering of plant, Undated (Box 11, Folder 04.16.07)
      - Miscellaneous black and white photos of plant equipment, Undated (Box 11, Folder 04.16.07)
      - Black and white photos of Corporate Headquarters, Undated (Box 11, Folder 04.16.07)
    - Production Shots
      - Five black and white photos of apple dump from "Life" magazine, Circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 04.17.01)
      - Two color and two black and white photos of Tree Top 6-ounce six-pack cans, Undated (Box 11, Folder 04.17.01)
      - Apples on tree, Undated (Box 11, Folder 04.17.01)
      - Pitcher and glasses with juice (no Tree Top containers), Undated (Box 11, Folder 04.17.01)
      - Apple crepes with instant Tree Top applesauce (2 photos), Undated (Box 11, Folder 04.17.01)
      - Pear, Undated (Box 11, Folder 04.17.01)
      - Cans of frozen cider with pitcher, Undated (Box 11, Folder 04.17.01)
      - Tree Top juice jars, Undated (Box 11, Folder 04.17.01)
      - Two black and white photos of Tree Top juice jars, Undated (Box 11, Folder 04.17.01)
      - Three jugs of Charbonneau Tree Top juice, Undated (Box 11, Folder 04.17.01)
      - Can of Charbonneau Tree Top juice, Undated (Box 11, Folder 04.17.01)
      - Bottle of Charbonneau Tree Top juice, Undated (Box 11, Folder 04.17.01)
      - Seven black and white photos of apple juice concentrate cans and juice, Undated (Box 11, Folder 04.17.01)
      - Boxes of "Fruit 'n Grape," "Fruit 'n Apple," and "Fruit 'n Berry.", Undated (Box 11, Folder 04.17.01)
      - Black and white stills from Tree Top television commercials (4 items), 1956-1960 (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
      - Tree Top Safeway Store displays that coordinate with Tree Top animated commercials (3 items), Spring 1957 (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
      - A woman picking apples (5 photos), 1956 October (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
      - Halloween grocery story display, Fall 1956 (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
      - Black and white photo of products that use Tree Top juice concentrates, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
      - Halloween Apple Cider grocery store display, 1972 October (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
      - 2 photos of grocery display at Thriftway, Yakima, WA, 1972 July (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
      - Tree Top grocery store display (unknown location), Circa 1972 (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
      - Tree Top juice display at San Francisco, Circa 1972 (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
      - 4 photos of Grocery Display, Circa 1970 (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
      - Tree Top Cider display at Rosauer's in Pullman, WA, 1972 October (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
      - Freezer sections from grocery store, Santa Rosa, CA, Circa 1970 (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
      - Mayfair apple cider grocery display, 1972 September (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
      - Grocery display at Lucky's in Bellevue, WA, 1972 September (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
      - Grocery display at Lucky's in Seattle, WA, 1972 October (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
      - Grocery display at Ralph's in Anaheim, CA, 1970 March (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
      - Grocery display at Ralph's in Palo Verde, CA, 1970 January (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
      - Grocery display at Ralph's in Encino, CA, 1980 May (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
      - Grocery store display at Ralph's in Granada Hills, CA, 1970 May (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
      - Black and white photo of woman serving Tree Top apple juice to a girl, Circa 1970 (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
      - Safeway store display, person dressed as a can of juice, Circa 1970 (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
      - Blue bucket with Tree Top, Welch's, Sacramento, Ocean Spray, and Donald Duck juice products, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
      - Pat Moss with crew from KCPQ Seattle at Corporate Offices, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
      - Brandi DeChenne, Miss Teen Washington 1997, Costume Award Winner (Tree Top Can), 1997 (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
      - Pear-grape cans, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
      - NRG smoothie stand, featuring Tree Top products (7 photos), Circa 1990s (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
      - Maid of Clover promotion, Circa 1980s (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
      - Cans of Juice Fizz, 1996 March (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
      - Fruit Rockets van and samples, Selah, WA, 2001 August (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
      - School promotion table, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.17.02)
    - Board Members and Growers (filed alphabetically; group photos are cross-listed and filed under the first name listed)
      - Allen, Bruce, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.01)
      - Auvil, Tom, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.02)
      - Bailey, Richard (Dick), Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.03)
      - Beckner, Jack, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.04)
      - Borton, John, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.05)
      - Braden, Peg, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.06)
      - Buck, Nancy, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.07)
      - Buckner, Lindsay, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.08)
      - Burnett, Hugh, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.09)
      - Burnett, Mark, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.10)
      - Callaway, Ryan, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.11)
      - Carlson, Sherman A, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.12)
      - Chapman, George, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.13)
      - Charbonneau, Mr. and Mrs. Bill, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.14)
      - Colbert, Ray, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.15)
      - Colleran, Dennis, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.16)
      - Collins, Darrell, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.17)
      - Conroy, Bob, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.18)
      - Corwin, Dick, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.19)
      - Davidson, Kenneth W, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.20)
      - Delgiorno, Mike (see Beckner, Jack), Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.21)
      - Dennis, Bob, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.22)
      - Dilschneider, Ray, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.23)
      - Draney, Kent, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.24)
      - Eder, Bruce, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.25)
      - Eisele, Tom, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.26)
      - Eisenheim, David, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.27)
      - Ellis, Terrie, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.28)
      - Elsner, Frank (see also Conroy, Bob), Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.29)
      - Ervant, Wally, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.30)
      - Fadden, Larry (see also Eisenheim, David), Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.31)
      - Flagg, Ronald W., Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.32)
      - Fossum, A.T. (see also Burnett, Hugh), Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.33)
      - Fraizer, Ron, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.34)
      - Gilbert, Cragg (see also Colbert, Ray and Colleran, Dennis), Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.35)
      - Godfrey, Bryce, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.36)
      - Hagerty, Dan, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.37)
      - Hargroves, Cathy, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.38)
      - Hinson, Ino, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.39)
      - Jeffries, Marvin J., Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.40)
      - Johnson, Charles (Chuck), Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.41)
      - Keller, Ray, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.42)
      - King, Glenn, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.43)
      - Kobes, Jerry (see Elsner, Frank and Eisele, Tom), Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.44)
      - Lamb, Lynne, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.45)
      - Lehner, Jordan, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.46)
      - Lin, Yu Ling, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.47)
      - Lowrie, Becky, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.48)
      - Matthes, Dorothy, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.49)
      - McCoy, Mike, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.50)
      - McDonald, Peggy, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.51)
      - McMurray, Tracey, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.52)
      - Morin, Joe, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.53)
      - Morris, Tom, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.54)
      - Moss, Pat, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.55)
      - Mungia, Araceli, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.56)
      - Olsen, Dick, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.57)
      - Olsen, Larry, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.58)
      - Ormiston, Orville (see also Gilbert, Cragg and Burnett, Hugh), Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.59)
      - Ozuna, Debbie, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.60)
      - Paschen, Charlena, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.61)
      - Perez, Olga, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.62)
      - Peters, Chuck (see also Olsen, Larry), Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.63)
      - Peterson, Bonnie, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.64)
      - Poulin, Diane, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.65)
      - Rawn, Ned, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.66)
      - Redmond, Bill, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.67)
      - Remington, Beth (see also Godfrey, Bryce), Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.68)
      - Robbins, Jim, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.69)
      - Seiger, Larry, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.70)
      - Serna, Arnie, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.71)
      - Slagg, Sarah, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.72)
      - Slowe, Barb, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.73)
      - Sowder, Rich, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.74)
      - Stockwell, Doug, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.75)
      - Stokes, Tom (see also Elsner, Frank), Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.76)
      - Strand, Roger, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.77)
      - Swedberg, Jeannie, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.78)
      - Taylor, Jeanne, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.79)
      - Town, Erin, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.80)
      - Tyrell-Smith, Tim (see Beckner, Jack), Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.81)
      - Twomey, John E, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.82)
      - Valentine, Fred (see also Jeffries, Marvin A.), Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.83)
      - Van Well, Pete (see also Olson, Larry), Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.84)
      - Verne, Steven, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.85)
      - Wangler, Kim (see Perez, Olga), Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.86)
      - Ward, Judi, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.87)
      - Wenzel, Jeff, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.18.88)
    - Group Shots
      - Grower relations committee: Chuck Peters, Ray Clbert, Fred Valentine, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.19.01)
      - Chuck Peters and Cragg Gilbert, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 04.19.02)
      - Tom Stokes and Bob Conroy, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.19.03)
      - Dennis Colleran and Pete Van Well, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.19.04)
      - Ron Flagg and Pat Moss, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.19.05)
      - Russ Jones, Louie Hauser and Jim Metlon, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.19.06)
      - Office Services: Sara Mabee, Ron Frazier, Teresa Trout, Becky Griffith, Kris McMahan (5 photos), 1999 January (Box 12, Folder 04.19.07)
      - Brenar Roddell, Bruce Cockett, and Tom Stokes, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.19.08)
      - Customer Service Reps: Tamara Tuttle, Misty Clements, Cindy Hanshew, Chartena Paschen (2 photos), 1998 October (Box 12, Folder 04.19.09)
      - Information Services: Teri Walton, Charlena Paschen, Glenn King, Tom Haile (2 photos), 2003 April (Box 12, Folder 04.19.10)
      - Brad Nelson and Ray Dilschneider, 1999 June (Box 12, Folder 04.19.11)
      - Debbie Hill, Lee Layman, Araceli Munguia, 1998 May (Box 12, Folder 04.19.12)
      - Tracey McMurray, Brena Rudell, Bruce Crockett, Tom Stokes, 2001 June (Box 12, Folder 04.19.13)
      - Ken Black, Diana Roeber, Rob Farrow (4 photos), 1998 August (Box 12, Folder 04.19.14)
      - Ing. Business Development Team, 2005 June (Box 12, Folder 04.19.15)
      - Annette Lane, Peg Braden, Debbie Hill, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 04.19.16)
      - Kent Draney, Jim Robbins, John McAllister, 1989 September (Box 12, Folder 04.19.17)
      - Leila Huri, Kent Draney, Pam Clark, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 04.19.18)
      - Tom Stokes, Chuck Johnson, Cathy Hargroves, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.19.19)
      - Frank Elsener, Jeff Wenzel, Ed Reinhart, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 04.19.20)
      - Information services: Teri Walton, Charlena Paschen, Glenn King, Tom Haile, 2003 April (Box 12, Folder 04.19.21)
      - Larry Olsen, George Chapman, Ray Colbert, Roger Strand, Pete Van Well, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.19.22)
      - Information Services: Kent Draney, Ken Keifenheim, David Eisenheim, Larry Fadden, Chris Kelley, Jim Kock, Laurie Buehler, Tom Haile, Larry Seiger, Jason Kelly, Rich Sowder, Jim Betts, 1997 June (Box 12, Folder 04.19.23)
      - Jason Whitman and Mike Box (3 photos), 2002 July (Box 12, Folder 04.19.24)
      - Marketing Department: Bruce and Peggy McDonald, Bryce Godfrey, Brooke Goodrich, Lisa Baldoz, Angelique Sabin, 2003 February (Box 12, Folder 04.19.25)
      - Tree Top Resource Group: Olga Perez, Kirk Jaocbson, Louis Hauser, Johnny Warren, Tod Pellaton, Georgia St. Aubyn, 1996 August (Box 12, Folder 04.19.26)
      - Tree Top Corporate Store: Sam (Phyllis Hoff and Peggy Williams (5 photos), 1996 May (Box 12, Folder 04.19.27)
      - Bill Waddoups and Dave Lewman (3 photos), 2003 August (Box 12, Folder 04.19.28)
    - Corporate Events
      - Carrier Appreciation Luncheon (5 photos), 2000 October (Box 12, Folder 04.20.01)
      - Walk America, Franklin Park, Yakima, WA, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 04.20.02)
      - Tree Top Carolers (4 photos), Mid-1990s (Box 12, Folder 04.20.03)
      - Employee Christmas Open House (3 photos), 2000 December (Box 12, Folder 04.20.04)
      - Selah Float, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 04.20.05)
      - Tree Top Silent Auction, 2001 June (Box 12, Folder 04.20.06)
      - Employee Christmas Open House (4 photos), 2000 December (Box 12, Folder 04.20.07)
      - Unidentified people at Employee Christmas Open House, taken by Hort Show (15 photos), 1999 December (Box 12, Folder 04.20.08)
      - Consumer packaged goods - Thanksgiving potluck (3 photos), 2000 November (Box 12, Folder 04.20.09)
      - Corporate Office Chili Contest (3 photos), Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.20.10)
      - Computer chair of toilet paper, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.20.11)
    - Field Services
      - Taken from Poirer Warehouse on Methow River near Pateros, WA (3 photos), Early 1990s (Box 12, Folder 04.21.01)
      - Northern Field Office, 1999 October (Box 12, Folder 04.21.02)
      - Mark Burnett, Northern Field Manager in orchard at Malott, WA (14 photos), Early 1990s (Box 12, Folder 04.21.03)
      - Undated orchard photos, Circa 1970s-1990s (Box 12, Folder 04.21.04)
      - Brian Wheeler, Pat Moss, and "Q Bird" with KCPQ-Seattle TV crew (6 photos), 1995 September (Box 12, Folder 04.21.05)
      - Shirley Brown with hail damaged fruit, 1997 September (Box 12, Folder 04.21.06)
      - Pictures of Orchard send to Boh Ward for Chicago (8 photos), Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.21.07)
      - Field Services Department: Bill Waddoups, Dave Lewman, Brian Wheeler, Pat Moss, Ross Todorovich, Koreen Brown, Roxie Asher, Mark Burnett, Lindsay Buckner, Phil Gutzwiler, Chuck Running, Darla Bennett, Dan Hankinson, Sue Matthews, Mickey Thompson, Margie Olivas, Tawnia Matthes, Shirley Brown. (7 photos), 1999 October (Box 12, Folder 04.21.08)
      - Early Freeze (2 photos), 2002 October (Box 12, Folder 04.21.09)
    - Tech Center
      - Black and white photos of interior of the tech center (4 photos), Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.22.01)
      - Black and white photo of Tom Eisele in the Tech tasting room, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.22.02)
      - Tom Eisele--tech center (4 photos), Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.22.03)
      - Jennie Bailey--consumer hotline (6 photos), 1997 April (Box 12, Folder 04.22.04)
      - Jennie Bailey-Eversole and Sonia Guitierrez--Consumer Affairs Department, 1993 March (Box 12, Folder 04.22.05)
      - Sandy Conrad, Debi Flores, Carmel Schroder, Leann Lange, 2001 August (Box 12, Folder 04.22.06)
      - Charlotte Duel--R and D (2 photos), 1980s (Box 12, Folder 04.22.07)
      - Midori Gibson (2 photos), Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.22.08)
      - Melinda Semon and Midori Gibson, 2002 August (Box 12, Folder 04.22.09)
      - Peggy Chambers and Shirley (Parker) Hall, 2002 August (Box 12, Folder 04.22.10)
      - Debbie Briesmeister and Jim Robbins, 2002 August (Box 12, Folder 04.22.11)
      - Sonia Nowlin and Teresa Streetwood, 2002 August (Box 12, Folder 04.22.12)
      - Sue Ibach--tech center; tasting, 1980s? (Box 12, Folder 04.22.13)
      - Sue Graf (2 photos), Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.22.14)
      - John Baranowski making Tree Top apple juice samples, 1990s? (Box 12, Folder 04.22.15)
      - children taste testing Tree Top apple juice (12 photos), 1990s? (Box 12, Folder 04.22.16)
      - Scott Summons (2 photos), Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.22.17)
    - Cashmere Plant
      - Interior of Cashmere Plant, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.23.01)
      - Cashmere City Waste Treatment Lagoon, (3 photos), 1973 July (Box 12, Folder 04.23.02)
      - Aerial photo of Cashmere Plant, 1973 June (Box 12, Folder 04.23.03)
      - Aerial shot, Cashmere Plant, (8 photos), 1976 May (Box 12, Folder 04.23.04)
      - Ivan Bowman, Joe Brooks, Nancy McGuire, Dean Falteisek, Penny Treider, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.23.05)
      - Ivan Bowman, Joe Brooks, Nancy McGuire, Penny Treider, Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.23.06)
      - Mary Broers, Sandra Mueller, Nancy McKinzie, Penny Treider, Ivan Bowman, Reulle Snelle, Dean Falteisek, Nancy McGuire, Deborah Eichler Burge, (2 photos), 1996 (Box 12, Folder 04.23.07)
      - Tanker of apple juice concentrate going to Rialto Plant for processing (10 photos), 2001 January (Box 12, Folder 04.23.08)
      - Bulk unloading, Circa 2001 (Box 12, Folder 04.23.09)
      - Loaded truck, Circa 2001 (Box 12, Folder 04.23.10)
    - Prosser Plant
      - Polu Urbina (2 photos), 1999 July (Box 12, Folder 04.24.01)
      - Marianne Esche (2 photos), 1999 July (Box 12, Folder 04.24.02)
      - Greg Elliot (2 photos), 1999 July (Box 12, Folder 04.24.03)
      - Phyllis Graham and Hazel Harvey (2 photos), 1999 July (Box 12, Folder 04.24.04)
      - Marianne Esche (2 photos), 1999 July (Box 12, Folder 04.24.05)
      - Tammy Smith (3 photos), 1999 July (Box 12, Folder 04.24.06)
      - Exterior (6 photos), 1999 July (Box 12, Folder 04.24.07)
      - Debbie Baker with colored-flavored sauce cups (3 photos), 1999 July (Box 12, Folder 04.24.08)
      - Fruit Rocketz Line (8 photos), 2001 April (Box 12, Folder 04.24.09)
      - Debbie Baker, Fruit Rocketz line (2 photos), 2001 April (Box 12, Folder 04.24.10)
      - Employee adjusting Fruit Rocketz line, 2001 April (Box 12, Folder 04.24.11)
    - Rialto Plant
      - Howard Talamantes (2 photos), Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.25.01)
      - Exterior view (4 photos), 1998 December (Box 12, Folder 04.25.02)
      - Running Tropicana Twister (13 photos), 1998 December (Box 12, Folder 04.25.03)
      - Bill Savage--Rialto Plant, 1998 December (Box 12, Folder 04.25.04)
      - Howard Talamantes and Bill Savage (3 photos), 1998 January (Box 12, Folder 04.25.05)
      - Plant interior (6 photos), 2001 January (Box 12, Folder 04.25.06)
      - Bottling line (9 photos), 2002 November (Box 12, Folder 04.25.07)
      - Interior of various plant machinery (3 photos), 2002 November (Box 12, Folder 04.25.08)
      - ESL class (5 photos), Undated (Box 12, Folder 04.25.09)
    - Ross Plant
      - Ross Plant Lab (2 photos), 1997 March (Box 12, Folder 04.26.01)
      - Ryan Kallenberger, Nicki Firman, Adrian Johnson, Phillip Brinson, Tony Landis, Pamelyn Moore, Clint McMurray. Drum Dry Team 1, 1997 March (Box 12, Folder 04.26.02)
      - Betty Baker, Mary Johnson, James Woodcock, Juanda Ayers, Manuel Rangel, John Schneider, Richard Townsend. Drum Dry Team 2, 1997 March (Box 12, Folder 04.26.03)
      - Ignacio Gonzalez, Nuno Fernandes, Anselmo Pena, David Abarca, Joyce Simmons, Jim Gallihan, John Drakes. Drum Dry Team 3, 1997 March (Box 12, Folder 04.26.04)
      - Doug Gentry, David Phillips, Sam Garcia, Lupe Trevino, Ray Schey, Ruben Gutierrez, Walter Cruz, Daniel Tanner. Drum Dry Team 4, 1997 March (Box 12, Folder 04.26.05)
      - Merle Frost and Carol Hyatt, 1997 October (Box 12, Folder 04.26.06)
      - Michael Voss, Ross Plant Wastewater Treatment Facility (3 photos), 1997 October (Box 12, Folder 04.26.07)
      - Ross Wastewater Treatment Facility (11 photos), 1997 October (Box 12, Folder 04.26.08)
      - Merle Frost and Carol Hyatt, Wastewater Operations Lab, 1997 October (Box 12, Folder 04.26.09)
      - Jeff Davis and Michael Voss, Wastewater Treatment Facility, 1997 October (Box 12, Folder 04.26.10)
      - Beverly Bliss, QA Tech (2 photos), 1999 October (Box 12, Folder 04.26.11)